Fardin Abyani

Software Engineer

+989174145030 fardin.abyani@hotmail.com Shiraz, Iran

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 7+ years of experience in .NET development and leading product cycle from concept through to development and delivery. Highly experience in relational databases. Skilled in providing technical mentorship, resulting in improved code quality, system reliability, and team productivity.

EXPERIENCE

09/2022 - Present System Administrator

Sana Rayanesh Betis, Shiraz

07/2021 - 07/2022 **Conscription**

Compulsory military service

I have been passing my compulsory military service.

06/2019 - 05/2021 System Administrator and SQL Developer

Tarahan Sazesh Rayn Raybod, Shiraz

- · Learning Windows and Linux administration
- · Managing servers and systems
- · Performance tuning and query optimization

12/2017 - 06/2019 **SQL Developer / Team Lead**

Tarahan Sazesh Rayn Raybod, Shiraz

- Team leader for new development (Web Application version) of hospital information system (HIS)
- Database design and SQL development of hospital information system (HIS)

MS SQL Server

12/2014 - 12/2017 . **NET Software Developer**

Tarahan Sazesh Rayn Raybod, Shiraz

· Development of warehouse management software with accounting

Windows Application, C# .NET, MS SQL Server

· Performance tuning company's old software

Multi-Threading and Parallel Programming

 Development of an application which archive old paper official documents in the form of images in order to access data from all branches securely

Windows Application, C# .NET, MS SQL Server

• Development of some modules in a hospital information system (HIS)

Windows Application, C# .NET

EDUCATION

2020 Computer Software Engineering

Islamic Azad University, Shiraz

Bachelor

COURSES AND TRAINING

04/2017 - 08/2017 Android Mobile App Development & Java

02/2015 - 07/2015 PHP & My SQL

06/2012 - 09/2012 **Java Standard Edition (Basic)**

SKILLS

C# Advanced Windows Administration Advanced

SQL Advanced Linux Administration Intermediate

Java SE Intermediate

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Persian Native